It's ancient server
just fix this okay hello sir how are you doing belt loop I'm doing well how you
doing today okay you saw open panel or do you know who I of me oh I think I well
I was not subscribed to you but I found you on the uh I saw you on the what was
Well, how are you? Have you heard of you haven't heard of Seiki awakens or cult of Seiki have you?
I can't say that I have but you know, I'm always interested in meeting new folks. Um, it's you know, I
Try to keep them open mind. I don't I can't say that I'm
Can't say I'm
Really into a lot of that, you know that that way of thinking what have you but you know
Maybe conservative am I am I right or am I wrong? Yeah, I tend to be a bit conservative, but I have some liberal values as well
Um, you know, I've got some use that many people would say was a liberal and
You know, I do tend to be you know, I'm a southerner. I'm a redneck. I'm a police officer
So, okay officer. That's cool. You're authentic police officer
I've known some big police officers on my on my panel, but it's nice to have a authentic one
Well, I'm a police officer at a mental at a mental hospital. Okay
I have gone through the police academy and I'm a certified police officer.
I've been doing that for about 11 years now.
Oh, wow. Okay.
So they have their own police force,
the mental facility?
Yeah. Mental hospital.
Mental hospital. Wow.
That must be interesting work.
You might as well busy.
A good days when we aren't.
It is what you're not busy. Okay. Yeah, I mean it varies some days are busier than others and you know
Truthfully we you know we do all sorts of things like I
Mean we do the transportation after we have a transportation department, but they tend to leave at about 430 so we're anlet
we
did where the first responder when it comes to if there's a
uh, fire breaks out or, you know, um, we, we can actually have several hats that we handle.
Uh, yeah, well, you seem pretty interesting. Uh, you want to, you want to tell what state you're in,
or you don't want to tell them much, you know, how to, but I'm in Mississippi.
I'm in Mississippi. Okay, great. Well, nice southern, nice southern gentleman.
Well, can I ask what state you in I think California, California, okay?
Liberal California, this is tricks my cat right here saying hello you
I'm familiar with
California, I know a few folks from there and back
We just had a fella a friend of mine
that is
It was from San Diego area, moved out to Missouri and and so I just went and saw him over at another friend of mine's place down in Texas.
Oh, great. I know a lot of Texas people and some California people. I'm in Los Angeles in the South Bay of Los Angeles and in a beautiful redondo beach.
In the South Bay, I'm a terror reader. I've actually I had a YouTube channel for over a year a monetized channel
It just got deleted. And so this is my my new backup channel
I'm kind of starting from scratch a little bit, but I also am not because
You know, I have about 500 people already, you know subscribed and I have some good people that followed me over and I
Monetize on this channel some other ways. I also have a website going and things like that. So it's not all
all bad, but when I see, I saw YouTube police, I was like,
uh-oh, maybe I'd like to talk to the YouTube police,
and of course you can never,
everything's just automated now, it's just complete.
Well, I've got about five channels,
I just happened to be on that one
when I was scrolling through the live streams.
My main channel is about Luke 29.
Okay, do you do content or are you? Yeah, I do. Okay. Well, I'd like you to
Be able to share your channel and everything and give you a little promotion. What do you kind of things you cover on your channel?
Well, hey what hang on now just so you can follow my main channel back off flip over
Okay, and say something in chat
There we go
It is a monetized channel
Yeah
Been doing it for a couple years and we don't really have a I don't have a whole lot of direction in what I do
The fact is you could see me do a video on my dogs next when something about
You know cooking something or hanging out at the restaurant or
Lately we went to this past weekend. We went to a Renaissance festival and I see a whole bunch of videos about that
so
Like those Renaissance stairs that they're pretty fun. You can
They are we went to the largest one in the US. It's in Todd Mission, Texas
Okay
Wow, like did you dress up at all or some people like to dress up? You're authentically or
Are you there and playing clothes?
I had I think uh
I've got a skull cap with bow skulls on it and I had a leather vest from
You know when I used to ride my Harley and I had a shirt on said something about
something about Pirates because it was Pirate Day and
You know, I even had a little cuff earring on with a little anchor on
So I did a little dressing up my buddy did a
Devil dog did a better job in fact he was I think he was what you call a California
Marine or Hollywood Marine, I think right well devil dog. I'm not familiar with the term devil dog
And that doesn't do it to the Marines, correct? They're
the Marines got the nickname devil dogs from the Germans in
World War one in the battle of bellow woods
They would call them two full fundings and that trend roughly translated as devil dogs
Okay
That is his channel devil dollars. I hate to let you I hate to let you go so quick
I have to end the stream real quick. I'm so sorry, but please come back soon. Okay. It's good making you
All right. Thank you so much
One second just ending my stream, okay